<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-06-10T00:31:43+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">50 points worth reading everyday</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/50points/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="50 points worth reading everyday"/><published>2023-06-09T20:26:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-06-09T20:26:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/50points</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/50points/"><![CDATA[<p>Henry Cavill’s 50 Points Of Advice From An 80-Year-Old Man</p> <ol> <li> <p>Have a firm handshake</p> </li> <li> <p>Look people in the eye</p> </li> <li> <p>Sing in the shower</p> </li> <li> <p>Own a great stereo system</p> </li> <li> <p>If in a fight, hit first and hit hard</p> </li> <li> <p>Keep secrets</p> </li> <li> <p>Never give up on anybody. Miracles happen every day. (See no.17)</p> </li> <li> <p>Always accept an outstretched hand</p> </li> <li> <p>Be brave. Even if you’re not, pretend to be. No one can tell the difference.</p> </li> <li> <p>Whistle</p> </li> <li> <p>Avoid sarcastic remarks</p> </li> <li> <p>Choose your life’s mate carefully. From this one decision will come 90 per cent of all your happiness or misery.</p> </li> <li> <p>Make it a habit to do nice things for people who will never find out</p> </li> <li> <p>Lend only those books you never care to see again</p> </li> <li> <p>Never deprive someone of hope; it might be all that they have</p> </li> <li> <p>When playing games with children, let them win</p> </li> <li> <p>Give people a second chance, but not a third</p> </li> <li> <p>Be romantic</p> </li> <li> <p>Become the most positive and enthusiastic person you know</p> </li> <li> <p>Loosen up. Relax. Except for rare life-and-death matters, nothing is as important as it first seems.</p> </li> <li> <p>Don’t allow the phone to interrupt important moments. It’s there for our convenience, not the caller’s.</p> </li> <li> <p>Be a good loser</p> </li> <li> <p>Be a good winner</p> </li> <li> <p>Think twice before burdening a friend with a secret</p> </li> <li> <p>When someone hugs you, let them be the first to let go</p> </li> <li> <p>Be modest. A lot was accomplished before you were born.</p> </li> <li> <p>Keep it simple</p> </li> <li> <p>Beware of the person who has nothing to lose</p> </li> <li> <p>Don’t burn bridges. You’ll be surprised how many times you have to cross the same river.</p> </li> <li> <p>Live your life so that your epitaph could read, “No Regrets”</p> </li> <li> <p>Be bold and courageous. When you look back on life, you’ll regret the things you didn’t do more than the ones you did.</p> </li> <li> <p>Never waste an opportunity to tell someone you love them</p> </li> <li> <p>Remember no one makes it alone. Have a grateful heart and be quick to acknowledge those who helped you.</p> </li> <li> <p>Take charge of your attitude. Don’t let someone else choose it for you.</p> </li> <li> <p>Visit friends and relatives when they are in hospital; you need only stay a few minutes</p> </li> <li> <p>Begin each day with some of your favorite music</p> </li> <li> <p>Once in a while, take the scenic route</p> </li> <li> <p>Send a lot of Valentine cards. Sign them, ‘Someone who thinks you’re terrific.’</p> </li> <li> <p>Answer the phone with enthusiasm and energy in your voice.</p> </li> <li> <p>Keep a note pad and pencil on your bed-side table. Million-dollar ideas sometimes strike at 3 a.m.41. Show respect for everyone who works for a living, regardless of how trivial their job</p> </li> <li> <p>Send your loved ones flowers. Think of a reason later.</p> </li> <li> <p>Make someone’s day by paying the toll for the person in the car behind you</p> </li> <li> <p>Become someone’s hero</p> </li> <li> <p>Marry only for love.</p> </li> <li> <p>Count your blessings.</p> </li> <li> <p>Compliment the meal when you’re a guest in someone’s home.</p> </li> <li> <p>Wave at the children on a school bus.</p> </li> <li> <p>Remember that 80 percent of the success in any job is based on your ability to deal with people.</p> </li> <li> <p>Don’t expect life to be fair.</p> </li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Henry Cavill’s 50 Points Of Advice From An 80-Year-Old Man]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Read Books about Investment</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/finance/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Read Books about Investment"/><published>2023-05-18T17:37:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-18T17:37:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/finance</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/finance/"><![CDATA[<p>Read Books about Investment</p> <p>I read books such as One up on Wall Street, Security Analysis. Here are the information I find helpful.</p> <ol> <li> <p>When the rate is high, there are some stocks undervalued.</p> </li> <li> <p>Earning is more important than stock price.</p> </li> <li> <p>If you want to make money, you must be smarter than managers that hold a large of stocks. Similarly, if you want to get your paper accepted, you must be better than reviewer, at least one of your co-authors is.</p> </li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read Books about Investment]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Management</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/rl/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Management"/><published>2023-05-14T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-14T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/rl</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/rl/"><![CDATA[<p>Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Management</p> <p>Time series neural networks performs much better than MLP and buy and hold strategy for portfolio management.</p> <p>From the figure, we can learn that the DQN model has a good prediction of the future stock price and makes the right decision.</p> <p>It is interesting to know that the DQN model also holds a lot of cash based on the current model.</p> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/portfolio-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/portfolio-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/portfolio-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/portfolio.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1 center" width="400" height="500" title="example image" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Management]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Business plan for tea haven</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/businessplan/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business plan for tea haven"/><published>2023-03-08T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-08T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/businessplan</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/businessplan/"><![CDATA[<p>slogan: Come for the Tea, Stay for the Experience</p> <h2 id="executive-summary">Executive Summary:</h2> <p>Our tea house, named “Xiao Xiao Shen Tea Haven,” will be located in a prime commercial area, targeting individuals (students, parents, care givers, workers) who are looking for a cozy and tranquil environment to relax and enjoy high-quality tea, pastries, and light meals. We will offer a unique and diverse selection of tea blends from different regions of the world, paired with delicious pastries and light meals, to provide an unforgettable experience to our customers.</p> <p>It reserves a nice place for kids for a quiery time. Our tea house can host private parties.</p> <h2 id="market-analysis">Market Analysis:</h2> <p>Our target market will consist of individuals who are looking for a serene and inviting environment to unwind and relax with friends, colleagues, or alone. We will position ourselves as a premium tea house, providing high-quality teas, pastries, and light meals that cater to the tastes and preferences of our customers. We will also focus on building strong relationships with our customers by offering personalized service, loyalty programs, and discounts.</p> <h2 id="products-and-services">Products and Services:</h2> <p>Our tea house will offer a wide range of tea blends sourced from different regions of the world, including black tea, green tea, white tea, oolong tea, herbal tea, and fruit tea. We will also offer pastries, such as scones, muffins, cakes, and cookies, as well as light meals such as sandwiches, salads, and soups. We will focus on providing high-quality products by sourcing our ingredients from reputable suppliers and ensuring our teas and food are made fresh daily.</p> <h2 id="marketing-and-sales">Marketing and Sales:</h2> <p>To promote our tea house, we will utilize various marketing strategies, such as social media advertising, local events, flyers, and promotions. We will also focus on creating a cozy and welcoming atmosphere in our tea house that encourages customers to come back and refer us to their friends and family. Additionally, we will leverage customer feedback to improve our services continually.</p> <h2 id="operations">Operations:</h2> <p>We will operate seven days a week, offering extended hours during weekends and holidays to cater to the needs of our customers. We will also focus on providing personalized services to our customers, such as customized tea blends, allergy-friendly pastries and light meals, and private event reservations.</p> <h2 id="financial-plan">Financial Plan:</h2> <p>Our startup costs will include equipment, rent, inventory, and initial marketing expenses. We will also hire a small team of staff, including a tea master, pastry chef, and servers. Our revenue streams will be from the sales of tea, pastries, and light meals. We expect to reach our break-even point within the first year of operation and achieve profitability within the second year.</p> <h2 id="conclusion">Conclusion:</h2> <p>In conclusion, Tea Haven will provide a unique and memorable experience for tea lovers, offering high-quality teas, pastries, and light meals in a cozy and inviting atmosphere. We believe that by focusing on quality, customer service, and personalized experiences, we will stand out from our competitors and become a popular destination for tea enthusiasts in our target market.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[slogan: Come for the Tea, Stay for the Experience]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Business plan for fintech</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/network/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Business plan for fintech"/><published>2023-03-08T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-08T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/network</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/network/"><![CDATA[<p>slogan: Navigate the Unknown with Xiao Xiao Shen</p> <h2 id="executive-summary">Executive Summary:</h2> <p>Our forecasting service, named “EcoPro” will provide businesses with accurate and reliable insights into future trends and market conditions. By utilizing advanced data analytics and machine learning techniques, we will offer customized forecasting solutions that meet the unique needs of our clients. We will position ourselves as a leader in the industry, providing high-quality forecasting services that help businesses make informed decisions and achieve their strategic goals.</p> <h2 id="market-analysis">Market Analysis:</h2> <p>Our target market will consist of businesses across various industries, including finance, restaurant, retail, healthcare, and manufacturing. We will focus on businesses that require accurate and reliable forecasting solutions to make strategic decisions, such as market trends, consumer behavior, and supply chain management. Our services will be particularly valuable to businesses that rely on accurate forecasts to optimize their operations and increase profitability.</p> <h2 id="products-and-services">Products and Services:</h2> <p>We will offer customized forecasting solutions that meet the specific needs of our clients. Our services will include data analysis, predictive modeling, trend analysis, and scenario planning. We will also provide regular updates and reports to our clients, keeping them informed of any changes in market conditions or trends.</p> <h2 id="marketing-and-sales">Marketing and Sales:</h2> <p>To promote our forecasting service, we will utilize various marketing strategies, such as social media advertising, webinars, conferences, and referral programs. We will also leverage our network of contacts in various industries to build relationships and generate leads. Additionally, we will offer a free trial of our services to potential clients to demonstrate the value of our forecasting solutions. We can work as long-term or short-term contractor to understand the request of the clients.</p> <h2 id="operations">Operations:</h2> <p>Our team will consist of experienced data analysts and machine learning experts who have a deep understanding of forecasting techniques and their applications. We will use advanced technologies and software to analyze data, build predictive models, and generate insights. We will also focus on providing excellent customer service, including personalized support and consultation, to ensure that our clients receive the best possible forecasting solutions.</p> <h2 id="financial-plan">Financial Plan:</h2> <p>Our startup costs will include equipment, software, marketing, and personnel expenses. We will also invest in converting publications to business directly.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[slogan: Navigate the Unknown with Xiao Xiao Shen]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Food protection manager certificate</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/foodprotectionmanager/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Food protection manager certificate"/><published>2023-03-01T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-03-01T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/foodprotectionmanager</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/foodprotectionmanager/"><![CDATA[<p>Today I got my food protection manager certificate. It is valid for 5 years. I prepared the courses by downloading the free learning <a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/business/health-academy/food-protection-online-free.page">resources</a> from NYC health. I learned the knowledge about food storage, allergens, cleaning, facilities, and personal hygiene. It is beneficial for me to process food correctly at home.</p> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/JW_Certificate-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/JW_Certificate-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/JW_Certificate-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/JW_Certificate.jpeg" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1 center" width="400" height="500" title="certificate" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I got my food protection manager certificate. It is valid for 5 years. I prepared the courses by downloading the free learning resources from NYC health. I learned the knowledge about food storage, allergens, cleaning, facilities, and personal hygiene. It is beneficial for me to process food correctly at home.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">An economic and RL related investing project</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/ecproject/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An economic and RL related investing project"/><published>2023-02-10T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-02-10T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/ecproject</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2023/ecproject/"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Learning to Navigate Wikipedia by Taking Random Walks <a href="https://nips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/53202.png?t=1668620595.2021506">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=wGF5mreJVN">paper</a> <ul> <li> <p>Connecting the Dots: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Graph Neural Networks <a href="https://github.com/nnzhan/MTGNN">Code</a> <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3394486.3403118">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Discrete Graph Structure Learning for Forecasting Multiple Time Series <a href="https://github.com/chaoshangcs/GTS">Code</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.06861">paper</a></p> </li> </ul> </li> <li> <p>Self-Supervised Aggregation of Diverse Experts for Test-Agnostic Long-Tailed Recognition <a href="https://nips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/55388.png?t=1668222168.065988">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=m7CmxlpHTiu">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Self-Supervised Contrastive Pre-Training For Time Series via Time-Frequency Consistency <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=OJ4mMfGKLN">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Uplifting Bandits <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=TIPyxNbzeB8">paper</a></p> </li> <li>Instance-optimal PAC Algorithms for Contextual Bandits <a href="https://neurips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/52901.png?t=1669512950.9225142">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=R1fj6401HJF">paper</a></li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Navigate Wikipedia by Taking Random Walks poster paper Connecting the Dots: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Graph Neural Networks Code paper]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Interesting papers in Neurips 2022</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/neurips/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Interesting papers in Neurips 2022"/><published>2022-11-30T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-30T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/neurips</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/neurips/"><![CDATA[<ul> <li>Learning to Navigate Wikipedia by Taking Random Walks <a href="https://nips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/53202.png?t=1668620595.2021506">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=wGF5mreJVN">paper</a> <ul> <li> <p>Connecting the Dots: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Graph Neural Networks <a href="https://github.com/nnzhan/MTGNN">Code</a> <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3394486.3403118">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Discrete Graph Structure Learning for Forecasting Multiple Time Series <a href="https://github.com/chaoshangcs/GTS">Code</a> <a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2101.06861">paper</a></p> </li> </ul> </li> <li> <p>Self-Supervised Aggregation of Diverse Experts for Test-Agnostic Long-Tailed Recognition <a href="https://nips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/55388.png?t=1668222168.065988">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=m7CmxlpHTiu">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Self-Supervised Contrastive Pre-Training For Time Series via Time-Frequency Consistency <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=OJ4mMfGKLN">paper</a></p> </li> <li> <p>Uplifting Bandits <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=TIPyxNbzeB8">paper</a></p> </li> <li>Instance-optimal PAC Algorithms for Contextual Bandits <a href="https://neurips.cc/media/PosterPDFs/NeurIPS%202022/52901.png?t=1669512950.9225142">poster</a> <a href="https://openreview.net/forum?id=R1fj6401HJF">paper</a></li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning to Navigate Wikipedia by Taking Random Walks poster paper Connecting the Dots: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Graph Neural Networks Code paper]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Attend Harvard Data Science Initiative Conference 2022</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/hsdi/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Attend Harvard Data Science Initiative Conference 2022"/><published>2022-11-17T18:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-17T18:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/hsdi</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/hsdi/"><![CDATA[<p>We drive 4 hours from NYC to the Harvard campus. The location of the conference is in Harvard University. But we stayed in the hotel next to the MIT campus. My friend Professor Christopher Musco gave me some recommendations about things to do near MIT.</p> <p>The conference is hosted by Professor David C. Parkes. I met experts from AWS and other companies, such as Nelson González, famous professors from multiple universities. The professors introduce their interesting works published in papers or reported by News. The interesting topics include utilizing AI to make fair decisions in human related experiments, AI helping Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) investing, and educating the public of Covid with Statistical Visualization.</p> <p>The last panel provides the postdoctoral researchers at Harvard University the opportunity to introduce their works. Some of them have already offered faculty positions.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[We drive 4 hours from NYC to the Harvard campus. The location of the conference is in Harvard University. But we stayed in the hotel next to the MIT campus. My friend Professor Christopher Musco gave me some recommendations about things to do near MIT.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Economics Computation</title><link href="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/ec/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Economics Computation"/><published>2022-11-12T11:22:00+00:00</published><updated>2022-11-12T11:22:00+00:00</updated><id>https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/ec</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://jingwang-ru.github.io/blog/2022/ec/"><![CDATA[<p>At Amazon retail, the people with Ph.D. degree in Economics and Computer Science are assigned with the same title, applied scientist. I realize the importance of Economics knowledge at work, start to learn by myself. I read books of Professor N. Gregory Mankiw, such as “Principles of Economics”, “Macroeconomics”. It pointed out that tech companies hire Economics because the companies are as powerful or rich as a country. I have a second thought about the power of tech companies when the actions of the Federal Reserve lead to layoffs recently. One rule impresses me is that the time spent on the course is related to the final score. Later, I am lucky to get suggestions from Professor Garrett van Ryzin, and Professor Itai Ashlagi.</p> <p>I read more papers of EC and listen to some talks on youtube channel “ACM SIGecom”. One of the keynote speaker of EC’22 is Professor Michael Jordan. He said his paper is rejected by EC because he considered the market with no money which is not interesting to EC people. He also mentioned the connections of the three foundational discriplines “Statistics”, “Computer Science” and “Economics” as shown below.</p> <div class="row"> <div class="col-sm mt-3 mt-md-0"> <figure> <picture> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 480px)" srcset="/assets/img/ec-480.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="/assets/img/ec-800.webp"/> <source class="responsive-img-srcset" media="(max-width: 1400px)" srcset="/assets/img/ec-1400.webp"/> <img src="/assets/img/ec.png" class="img-fluid rounded z-depth-1 center" width="400" height="500" title="example image" onerror="this.onerror=null; $('.responsive-img-srcset').remove();"/> </picture> </figure> </div> </div> <p>Professor Michael Jordan also introduces his team’s work</p> <ol> <li>Statistical Contract Theory by Stephen Bates, Michael Sklar and Jake Soloff, e.g. “Mechanisms that incentivize data sharing in federated learning”</li> <li>Strategic Classification by Tijana Zrnic and Eric Mazumdar</li> <li>Competing Bandits in Matching Markets by Lydia Liu and Horia Mania</li> <li>Learning Equilibria in Matching Markets from Bandit Feedback by Meena Jagadeesan, Alex Wei, Yixin Wang and Jacob Steinhardt</li> <li>Distribution-Free Uncerntainty Quantification for Decision-Making by Anastasios Angelopolous, Stephen Bates, Emmanuel Candes, and Lihua Lei. One-dimensional functional.</li> </ol>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Amazon retail, the people with Ph.D. degree in Economics and Computer Science are assigned with the same title, applied scientist. I realize the importance of Economics knowledge at work, start to learn by myself. I read books of Professor N. Gregory Mankiw, such as “Principles of Economics”, “Macroeconomics”. It pointed out that tech companies hire Economics because the companies are as powerful or rich as a country. I have a second thought about the power of tech companies when the actions of the Federal Reserve lead to layoffs recently. One rule impresses me is that the time spent on the course is related to the final score. Later, I am lucky to get suggestions from Professor Garrett van Ryzin, and Professor Itai Ashlagi.]]></summary></entry></feed>